Bicycle or something came through here.
That's a letdown.
Just looks like a whole lot of nothing out here.
Hmm?
Raccoon dog.
See the antlers? I'm a reindeer!
I saw you fall! Are you hurt?
Who the heck is that?
What's going on?
Do you mind? I was sleeping.
Did you hit my friend?
Oh, man! That guy is huge!
I thought we were alone on this island.
Huh?
You know him?
Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji,
the ferocity of an ultimate powerhouse.
This guy has Robin scared out of her freaking mind!
Why?
He's a Marine.
Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji.
Admiral?
Wait, you mean this guy's an admiral?
That's one of the highest ranks there is!
That's right, there are only three officers in the entire navy who currently hold the position of admiral.
Akainu, Aokiji, and Kizaru.
The only one who outbreaks them is Fleet Admiral Sengoku, the navy's top official.
The man you see standing before you is one of the three men known as the world government's ultimate powerhouses.
But why in the heck is someone like this even here?
Shouldn't you be out hunting some big-time pirates with a bazillion berry bounties or something?
Go away!
Huh?
Oh, my, my.
What? What is it?
Another very sexy lady with super big bazongas.
Are you free tonight?
You watch your mouth, you lanky jerk!
Focus! Pay attention!
Whoa, whoa, hold on a second, you guys.
Couldn't you hear what I just said?
I'm just out taking a little stroll.
Don't get so worked up, okay?
I mean, you guys are just...
You're like just whatchamacallits, you know?
What?
What'd he say?
Mmm...
I forgot. Oh, well.
You're not making any sense, you weirdo!
Robin, are you kidding?
You must be mistaking him for someone else.
This doofus wouldn't pass for a regular marine, let alone an admiral.
Hey, come on.
You shouldn't go around judging people based on their appearance.
The motto I've always lived by as a marine is total, slovenly justice.
Then our judgment was right!
Anyway, what I was saying...
Uh, excuse me a moment.
Being on my feet too long makes me tired.
Yeah? Then maybe you shouldn't have been sleeping standing up, you think?
What I was saying is that I have no intention of capturing you or anything like that, so just take it easy.
I'm only here to confirm the whereabouts of Nico Robin, who hadn't been seen since the Alabaster incident.
As we suspected, she's been with you.
That is one tall piece of apathy.
The only thing high-ranking about him is his nerve.
I'll put some sort of report together for headquarters later.
Now that you've added another crew member who's got a price on her head, your overall bounty has gone up.
One hundred million plus sixty million plus seventy-nine million equals...
Ah, screw it. Some big-ass number.
Just do the damn math.
That's it! Come, go!
Hold on, Yiffy!
Stop it! Stop!
What are you guys doing? Let me go!
Why are you trying to start a fight with this guy?
Are you crazy? He's one of the strongest Marines there is!
I'm not just gonna stand around while this jerk tries to take Robin away from us!
Take it easy. I told you I'm not gonna do anything, remember?
Well, I am! I'm kicking your ass!
Stop it! Damn it! Hold on! Just relax!
So you're really a Marine? I wish we'd known that a lot sooner.
Hey, who are all these people?
Whoa, are you guys okay?
I thought this island was uninhabited.
Well, they're probably castaways that washed up on the shore here.
There was a passenger liner that was reported missing about a month ago, last seen somewhere in this area.
I'm guessing it sank, and these are the survivors.
How are they, Chopper?
Some of them are injured, but it doesn't appear to be anything too serious.
I've got some medicine that should fix them right up.
But the more pressing matter is that they haven't had much to eat in days. Their bodies are weak.
Sanji and Usopp went to see if they could find some food. They should be back soon.
Hey! Sorry it took so long!
I can only imagine how hungry you are.
Take it easy. No need to wolf it down. There's plenty more where that came from.
Yeah, no wolf. There's plenty.
Hey! Why are you eating it? Cut it out!
Ugh. Look, this island may be deserted, but you still could have found food on your own, you know.
You're lucky we came along when we did.
Their ship wrecked in the Grand Line. They're lucky to be alive at all.
Not everyone was so fortunate. We were the only ones on the ship who made it to this island.
So what happened?
We were on our way home from a gourmet tour of Poochie, the city renowned for its exquisite food,
when suddenly our ship collided with a giant frog that was doing the front crawl and shattered it to pieces.
A giant frog doing the front crawl? Seriously?
Besides, frogs normally do the breaststroke.
Awesome! We have got to see this frog!
That sounds crazy.
It's the truth!
Yeah, that was Yokozuna.
Huh? Yokozuna?
After what seemed like days of struggling, we were finally able to make it to this island.
It didn't take long to deplete our food supply. After one month, we were on the brink of starvation.
Then we spotted someone approaching the island. We rejoiced until we noticed he was riding a bicycle on the water.
Come on! That's even more far-fetched than the frog!
Ah, that was me, actually.
Huh?
The only boat we spotted after that looked like a pirate ship.
That was us.
Well, that makes you one of those, uh, uh, those, you know...
Spit it out, damn it!
Oh, man, I forgot! Stop screwing us around, Jack!
Calm down, look at you! Get a hold of yourself! Take it easy!
Didn't you hear me?
I told you, I'm just out on a stroll.
A stroll, huh? Then go take your stroll somewhere else! Get out of here!
Why are you so angry at me?
It's like he's trying to pick a fight.
Okay, whatever. I'll leave, but before I do, you guys should gather your stuff and get ready to leave, too.
Fortunately, I know of an inhabited island that's not too far away from this one.
You should go there and ask him to help you out.
Hey, you guys! Don't believe a word he says! Understand me? This jerk's a marine officer!
So what? Is that a problem?
Oh, that's right. I get it. I guess that makes sense. Normally the marines are your friends and the pirates are the bad guys, right?
Stop it! What's so funny?
Him? How is he gonna help anybody?
I don't know. Heck, I don't even think he has a ship.
Other than ours, there isn't another ship around anywhere.
Let's see. There's no ship and nobody here seems to have a log pose either.
How in the world are they supposed to get to that island anyway?
Oh, they'll be fine.
Nothing you say sounds the least bit convincing.
It's true.
He does have the power to help them.
That should do it!
We loaded them up with food and water. It should be enough to last them for quite a while.
Feels good to do a little work from time to time.
Yeah, no doubt about that. Hey, you know something? You're not so bad.
What do you know? They're hitting it off.
Okay, so now what? Are you gonna swim to that island and drag these guys and all their stuff behind you?
Don't be ridiculous.
All right, everybody. Stay back.
What is that thing?
It's some kind of monster! I bet it's the guardian of this part of the sea!
Hey, you! Run for it! Look out!
Get out of there!
Ice Age!
A devil fruit!
The sea! It's... frozen!
This is the power of a Navy Headquarters Admiral.
Whew...
It'll stay like that for at least a week.
Head out across the sea in that direction. Take your time.
You should reach the island in about four days.
It's gonna be a little on the chilly side, so be sure to bundle up and stay warm.
Is this... a dream?
The sea has become as hard as the ground!
We can finally cross it! Now we'll be able to get off of this island!
Thank you! Thanks so much!
Thank you so much!
It's a miracle! The Marine granted us a miracle!
All right, then. Time for us to get going.
Right. I'm really happy for you guys. Take care!
I guess there are all sorts of different pirates, huh?
How can we ever thank you for everything that you've done for us?
Not only did you treat our sick and injured, but you shared your food and water with us as well.
Aw, don't worry about it!
Good things happen to good people. Just let fate take its course.
Make sure the children don't catch cold. Keep them bundled up tight!
At any rate, these colder temperatures should keep your food fresh longer.
Thank you all very much!
We will never forget your kindness!
Take care, Straw Hat Pirates!
Bye! Take care!
Be careful on your trip! Save journeys! Goodbye!
That felt really good!
It feels like winter just happened!
Check it out! I can skate!
Awesome, Chopper!
Must be that winter island blood!
How about this one?
You guys are trying to do!
Man, it's cold! I'm freezing!
What is it?
How should I put this?
You're the spitting image of your grandfather, Monkey D. Luffy.
Or maybe I should say, you're just as reckless and hard to figure out.
You knew... my grandpa!
Seriously? Luffy's?
Hey, Luffy, what's wrong? You're sweating!
Uh, nothing! Really! I'm fine!
Your grandfather helped me out once, a long time ago. That's why I'm here.
I wanted to see you and Nico Robin together with my own eyes.
On second thought, maybe I should just kill you.
The government still doesn't consider you a threat, but I know enough of your history to see you're a formidable crew.
You may be few in number, but with the shrewd rogues gathered here, this crew will likely be a problem later on.
Considering the circumstances regarding your initial bounty, the numerous daring actions you've taken, and the speed of your overall progress.
I've fought outlaws for most of my life, but thinking about how you'll turn out scares the hell out of me.
Hey, wait! Hold on a second! You said you were here to check things out, not to kill anyone!
One among you I consider the most dangerous. That would be you, Nico Robin.
So despite everything, you are here for Robin! Now I'm really gonna kick your ass!
The size of her bounty isn't merely a reflection of her strength and power. It also represents something else.
That would be the level of threat and danger that she poses to the world government.
That's why a 79 million Barry bounty was placed on her head at the tender young age of eight.
I'm impressed you were able to survive, especially as a child.
You managed to betray, sidestep, and escape from everyone in your past, and then found a new partner to make use of.
You survived in the underworld by being quick to switch sides, and now you've chosen this crew as your next haven.
That's enough, jerk! I'm not just gonna stand here and let you speak to a lady like that!
What kind of ridiculous grudge are you holding against Robin?
Stop it, Sanji!
I don't have anything against her.
The only connection we have between us is that I let her escape from me one time, but that's about it.
It was a long time ago.
You will all learn soon enough that protecting this troublesome woman leads to nothing but regret.
If you need proof, consider this.
Every organization that she's had something to do with in the past has been annihilated.
Not one single solitary member escaped except for her.
Why is that, Nico Robin?
Shut up, you jerk! The past doesn't matter!
That's right!
If it did, we wouldn't have a dangerous former pirate hunter guy or a degenerate conniving ex-thief woman on our crew, would we?
Don't go overboard!
Who we are now is more important than who we were.
That's right! Robin is our friend! Don't you dare say anything bad about her! You hear me?
I see. So these poor fools don't suspect a thing.
Just get to the point! If you want to arrest me, then why not just do it already?
Prince of Lu!
No! Robin!
My, my, my. Did something I say strike a nerve? That's too bad.
I must have overestimated how reasonable a woman you were.
And clutch!
He shattered into a million pieces!
It didn't work! We're screwed!
Let's get out of here, everybody! Run for your lives!
Now, now. That wasn't a very nice thing to do.
Ice Saber! I didn't want to have to kill you, but now.
I don't remember asking for your help, cook.
Funny, I was gonna say the same thing to you, Mosshead.
Come, go!
Stop!
I'm gonna go!
Keep going!
Come, go!
One!
Two!
They're so sad.
I didn't want to have to kill you, Mosshead.
One!
Two!
Three!
He froze him! He froze him!
He got all three of them at once!
He's freezing them solid! I have to help quickly!
If they get frostbite, their lips will start to run!
Ozop, what are you doing? We have to save them now!
I want to help. I'm trying to, but I can't see them move!
Did he freeze me too?
No, you're just too scared to move, coward!
Ah! Lupin!
Sanzi, don't know! Hold on! We'll save you!
Robin, run away!
You have some very loyal friends,
but you will never change, Nico Robin.
No, that's not true!
That's Robin! Get away from him! Watch out!
I'm not who I am!
Robin!
powers come hit with designer
technique!
Oh!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Oh, my God.
On the next One Piece, duel between rubber and ice, Luffy versus Aokiji.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!